Vonnegut, Bernard; Papers ua902.068
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Science Research and Inventions, 1828-1997; Undated; 6; 3.22 cubic ft.
  - Ball Lightning Project, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 12)
  - Ball Lightning Project, 1970-1972 (Flat-file 4)
  - Ball Lightning Project, 1971; Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 10)
  - Chaff Experiment, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 13)
  - Characteristics of Vertical Lightning, 1950-1951; 1987 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Foundation of Physics, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1955-1997 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 16)
  - Data, Multiple Projects, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 17)
  - Data, Multiple Projects, Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 14)
  - Davis, Gode "The Stormy Future of Weather Forecasting", 1991 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 18)
  - Davis, M.H. "The Present Status of Atmospheric Electricity", 1979 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 19)
  - Device to Detect Presence of Electrical Fields, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 20)
  - DMSP Satellite Photographs and Article Reprints, 1968; 1970; 1974 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 21)
  - DeVries, Tom "California Drought: can we change the weather before it's too late?", 1977 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 22)
  - Encyclopedia of Climate and Weather, 1990 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 23)
  - Howell/Eustis Patent Case, 1945-1987 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 24)
  - Feyman Lectures, 1964-1965; 1969 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 25)
  - G.E. Research Laboratory, 1947-1948; 1950-1951; Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 26)
  - Gedzelman, Stanley David "Science and Wonders of the Atmosphere", 1982 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 27)
  - Graph for Determining Height of Cloud Bases, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 28)
  - Instruments, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 29)
  - Invention: Aerosol Coagulator, 1970-1978 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 30)
  - Invention: Apparatus for Triggering Lightning, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 31)
  - Invention: Apparatus to Reduce Atmospheric Pollution Caused by Exhaust of Motor Vehicles, 1990 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 32)
  - Invention: Cloud LWC Sensor, 1977 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 33)
  - Invention: ICE detector, 1986 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 34)
  - Invention: Means and Methods for Detecting and Measuring Aerosols - - [RESTRICTED], 1954-1960 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 35)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Invention: Means and Methods for Producing Particles of High Charge Density, 1963; 1965 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 36)
  - Invention: Mechanical Means for Making Uniformly Sized Aerosols, 1962 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 37)
  - Invention: Method and Apparatus for Measuring the Concentration of Condensation Nuclei, 1949 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 38)
  - Invention: Microcell Instrument for Measurement of Electrical Conductivity of Cloud and Precipitation Water, 1978; 1987 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 39)
  - Invention: Microconductivity Cell for Real Time Measurements of the Electrical Conductivity of Cloud or Rain Water, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 40)
  - Invention: Monitor and Spectrometer for Atmospheric Particulate Matter, 1963; 1965 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 41)
  - Invention: Moisture Indicating Instrument, 1949 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 42)
  - Invention: Non-Conducting Fiber Electrometer, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 43)
  - Invention: Rainfall Intensity Sensor, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 44)
  - Invention: Tensiometer, 1951 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 45)
  - Invention: Vortex Whistle, 1953-1958 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 46)
  - Invention Records, 1933-1979 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 47)
  - Kamra, A.K., 1966-1983 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 48)
  - Kamra, A.K. "Dust Storm Electrification - Final Report to the National Science Foundation", 1971 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 49)
  - "Liebig & Whler" from A History of Chemistry, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 50)
  - Life Magazine, "American Production", 1948 (Oversized 3, Folder 15)
  - Lightning, 1920-1991 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 51)
  - Lightning during Yellowstone Fires, 1971; 1988 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 52)
  - Lightning Observations, 1980-1984 (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 53)
  - Lightning Preventions, Lightning Elimination Associates, Undated (Box 1 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 54)
  - Lightning Strikes to Aircraft, General, 1965-1977 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 1)
  - Lightning Strikes to Aircraft, General, 1965-1977 (Oversized 3, Folder 16)
  - Lightning Strikes to Aircraft, General, 1965-1977 (Flat-file 5)
  - Lightning Strikes to Aircraft - Salt Lake, "Frontier" Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 2)
  - McCownan, Dennis -Time Magazine, 1996 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 3)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 4)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1980-1981 (Oversized 3, Folder 17)
  - Mt. St. Helens, 1980-1981 (Oversized 4, Folder 11)
  - New York Times Articles on Weather, 1972-1986 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 6)
  - Oscillatory Anemometer, 1965-1995 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 7-8)
  - Oscillatory Anemometer Press Releases, 1988 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 9)
  - Patent Disclosures, 1973-1978 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 10)
  - Patents: General Electric, 1953-1959; 1980 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 11)
  - Patents: Multiple Inventions, 1949-1987 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 12-14)
  - Patents: Multiple Inventions, 1949-1987 (Flat-file 4)
  - Patents: Photocopies, 1922-1961 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 15)
  - Patents: Reprints, 1889; 1894; 1932-1966 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 16)
  - Photographs, 1961 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 17)
  - Photographs, 1965 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 18)
  - Photographs and Data, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 19)
  - Photographs: Airplane, 1955 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 20)
  - Photographs: Antique Scientific Apparatus, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 21)
  - Photographs: Apparatus Dept. Presentation, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 22)
  - Photographs: ASRC Experiment, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 23)
  - Photographs: Dr. Langmuir, Undated (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Floyd Montgomery, 1967 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 25)
  - Photographs: Heimaey, Iceland, 1973 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Instruments, 1955 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 27)
  - Photographs: Illinois, 1960 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 28-29)
  - Photographs:Life Filmstrip "The Mystery of Rain", 1962 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 30)
  - Photographs:Life Filmstrip "The Mystery of Rain", 1962 (Oversized 4, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Lightning, 1965 (Box 2 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 31)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 32)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Mt. Withington, 1962 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Radar, 1961 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Roger Jensen, Detroit Lakes MN - Cloud and Storm prints, 1958-1977 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Roy Arnold - Tornado, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Socorro, 1979 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Tornado, 1955 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Vortices, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Yellowstone, Undated (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 9)
  - Preston, F.W. and J.C. Turnbull "The Physics of Upward Drilling", 1941 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 10)
  - Princeton Pennsylvania Army Avionics Research Program, Final Task Report "A Fundamental Study of Static Electric Phenomena", 1972 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 11)
  - Reprints: Contrails, 1973 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 12)
  - Reprints: Convection and Convective Storms, 1973-1975 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 13)
  - Reprints: Electrical Measurements Above Thunderstorms, 1950; 1957; 1966 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 14)
  - Reprints: Electricity, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 15)
  - Reprints: Electrostatics, 1971; 1974-1975 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 16)
  - Reprints: Hailstorms, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 17)
  - Reprints: Satellite Observations, 1974 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 18)
  - Reprints: Silver Iodide, 1971-1975 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 19)
  - Reprints: Studies in the Early History of Surface Chemistry, 1969-1974 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 20)
  - Reprints: An Unusual Lightning flash at Kennedy Space Center, 1978 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 21)
  - Requests for Reprints of Papers and American Meteorological Association Speech, 1954-1955 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 22)
  - "Requirements for Electrification", 1971 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 23)
  - Royal Aircraft Incidents, 1958 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 24)
  - Scorer, R.S., Presidential Address, Royal Meteorological Society, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 25)
  - Smithsonian Aerophysical Observatory: Automatic Star Tracking System, 1959 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 26)
  - Snow, Snow Crystals, and Snow Storms, 1976 (Box 3 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 27)
  - Staples, Tad - Correlation between Thunder Pitch and Behavior of Storm, 1976 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 1)
  - Static Electricity, American Airlines, 1957 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 2)
  - Steacie, E.W.R. "Science, Society, and the Individual", 1959 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 3)
  - SUNY Research Publications, 1988 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 4)
  - Surtsey: Data and other associated documents, 1963-1964 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 5)
  - Surtsey: Photographs, 1963-1964 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 6-7)
  - Swiss Maps Transfer, 1970-1972 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 8)
  - Telephone Conversation with First Lt. Roger C. Gardner, Hurricane Hugo Lightning Observation, 1989 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 9)
  - Thunderstorm Electricity, Undated (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 10)
  - Thunderstorm Electrification and Cloud Physics, 1959-1996 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 11)
  - Tilson, Seymour "IEEE Spectrum", 1969 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 12)
  - U-2 Conductivity Meter, 1986 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 13)
  - U-2 Conductivity Meter, 1986 (Oversized 3, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Weather Research Program, 1996 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 14)
  - Vlcek, Charles L. "Observations of Sever Storms on 26 and 28 April 1971" NOAA Technical Memorandum ERL NSSL-63, 1973 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 15)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard "Physics and the Environment", 1994 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 16)
  - Vonnegut, Bernard "Determinants of Thunderstorm Dipole Polarity According to Influence Theories of Cloud Electrification", 1993 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 17)
  - Warm Cloud Lightning, 1950-1990 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 18)
  - Weisskopf, Victor F. "Of Atoms, Mountains, and Stars: A Study in Quantitative Physics", 1975 (Box 4 (6-General Science Research and Inventions), Folder 19)
- Manuscripts, 1867-1997; Undated; 7; 8.57 cubic ft.
  Series 7 consists of Dr. Vonnegut's published and unpublished articles, letters to the editor, papers, reviews, reports, and book/encyclopedia chapters. Many files contain the research and data discussed within the work, as well as correspondence with the editor(s) of publications where work was submitted.
  - Aerosol Monitor, 1961 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - AgI Toxicity Papers, 1968-1975 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2)
  - Agrometer Diagrams, Undated (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 3)
  - Airplane Instruments, 1955; Undated (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Arthur D. Little/Office of Naval Research Articles, 1953; 1956-1957 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Article: "A Laboratory Investigation of the Effect of Particle Collisions on the Generation of Electric Fields in Thunderstorms", 1970-1971 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Article: "A Technique for Measuring Relative Threshold Nucleation Temperatures for Active Nucleation Catalysts", 1972-1973 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - Article: "Abnormal Polarity of Thunderclouds that Grew from Negatively Charged Air", 1867; 1985-1986 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - Article: "Abnormal Polarity of Thunderstorms that Grew from Negatively Charged Air", Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 19)
  - Article: "Adhesive Behavior of Silicate Powders in Ultrahigh Vacuum", 1964 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Article: "Adirondack Conference on Electrostatics", 1969 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10)
  - Article: "Adjustable Potential-Gradient-Measuring Apparatus for Airplane Use", 1961 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 11)
  - Article: "Adventures in Fluid Flow; Generating Interesting Dendritic Patterns", 1996-1998 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12-13)
  - Article: "Aerometer for Measurement of Atmospheric Electrical Potential Gradient", 1961 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 14)
  - Article: "Airborne Filters for the Measurement of Atmospheric Space Charge", 1961 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Article: "Airplane Instrument for Measurement and Vectorial Presentation of Electrical Potential Gradient", 1960 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)
  - Article: "Airplane Instruments to Detect Ice Particles", 1988-1989 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Article: "Anomalous Electric Fields Associated with Clouds Growing Over a Source of Negative Space Charge", 1988-1989 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18)
  - Article: " Apparatus for Directly Measuring the Electrical Potential of the Ionosphere", 1958; 1969 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 19)
  - Article: "Apparatus for Measurements of the Electrical Conductivity of Rainwater with High Resolution in space and Time", 1991 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Article: "Apparatus for the stimulation of Rain in the Laboratory", 1980-1981 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - Article: "Apparatus Using Radioactive Probes for Measuring the Vertical Component of Atmospheric Potential Gradient from an Airplane", 1961 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Article: "Article Initiation of Lightning of Lighting Discharges", 1961 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Article: "Artificial Modification of Atmospheric Space Charge", 1962 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Article: "Artificial Stimulation of Rain", 1957 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Article: "Automatic Apparatus for Nucleation Investigations", 1981-1982 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Article: "Behavior of Evaporating Electrically Charged Droplets", 1963-1964 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27)
  - Article: "Biological Impact of Ions", 1976-1977 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 28)
  - Article: "Calcareous Incrustation Formed on Cascades at the Indiana State Soldiers and Sailors Monument, Indianapolis", Undated (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Article: "Calculation of Ice Enhancement Ratios", 1986-1987 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Article: "Cameras for Time-Lapse Photography", 1970 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Article: "A Capillary Collector for Measuring the Deposition of Water Drops on a Surface Moving through Clouds", 1949 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Article: "Charge Generation in Thunderstorms", 1963-1965 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Article: "Charge Transfer from a Highly Electrically Stressed Water Surface During Drop Impact", 1966; 1972-1973 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Article: "Charge Drops Produced by bursting of bubbles at the Surface of Organic Liquids", 1975-1977 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Article: "Charging of Droplets by Impulse Corona", 1970 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Article: "Chicken Plucking as a Measure of Tornado Wind Speed", 1975-1976 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 37)
  - Article: "Cloud Seeding", 1952 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 38)
  - Article: "A Cloud-to-Space Lighting as Recorded by the Space Shuttle Payload-Bay TV Cameras", 1992 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 39)
  - Article: "Cold Box Measurements of Cloud Particle Nuclei During CAPE", 1992-1993 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 40)
  - Article: "Comments on 'A Radar Study of the Plasma and Geometry of Lightning'", 1991 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 41)
  - Article: "Comment on 'Electrisation de Gouttes de solutions salines aqueuses Par Evaporation ou Par Condesation de la Vapeur D'eau'", 1977-1978 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 42)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Electrification of Condensing and Evaporating Liquid Drops'", 1973-1975 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 43)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Exchange Between Kamra and Saunders Concerning the Inducting Charging Mechanism in Thunderclouds'", 1978 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 44)
  - Article: "Comment on 'Factor of 2 Error in Balloon- borne, Atmospheric Conduction Current Measurements' by A.A. Few and J. J. Weinheimer'", 198-1987 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 45)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Ice Particle Concentration in Clouds'", 1987 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 46)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Ion-Drop Interaction During Drop Evaporation'", 1982-1984 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 47)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Need for Requirement the Details of Seeding Operations Be Adequately Specified'", 1985-1987 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 48)
  - Article: "Comment on Negatively Charged Precipitation in a New Mexico Thunderstorm", 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 1 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 49)
  - Article: "Comment on 'New Measurements of the Ion Content of Evaporation-Humidified Air'", 1979-1987 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Numerical Study of Cloud Electrification in an Axisymmetric, Time-dependent Cloud Model'", 1976; 1979 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Observations of Two Regions of Change During Initial Thunderstorm Electrification' by J.E. Dye, J.J. Jones, A.J. Weinheimer and W.P. Winn (July 1988, 114, 1271-1290)", 1988-1989; 1992 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 3)
  - Article: "Comment on 'On the Relation of Electrical Activity to Tornadoes' by R.P. Davies-Jones and J.H. Golden", 1975-1976 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Article: "Comments on 'A Quantitative Assessment of Precipitation Mechanisms of Thunderstorm Electrification'", 1971-1972 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Article: "Comments on 'A Radar Study of the Plasma and Geometry of Lightning'", 1989-1990 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Article: "Comment on 'A Review of Thunderstorm Electrification Processes'", 1992; 1994-1995 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - Article: "Comment on 'Solar Wind Mechanism Suggested for Weather and Climate Change' by Brian A. Tinsley, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Stratospheric Conductivity Variations Over Thunderstorms' by R.H. Holzworth, K.W. Norville, P.M. Kintner, and S.P. Powell", 1980; 1986-1987 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Article: "Comment on 'Stratosphere-troposphere Exchange in a Midlatitude Mesoscale Convective Complex'", 1996-1997 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10)
  - Article: "Comment on 'The Electrification of Thunderclouds and the Rain Gush' by Z. Levin and A. Ziv", 1974-1975 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 11)
  - Article: "Comment on the Paper 'The Electrification of Thunderstorms' by John Latham", 1981-1983 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12)
  - Article: "Comments on The 'Rain Gush' Lightning and the Lower Positive Charge Center in Thunderstorms' by E.R. Jayaratne and C.P.R Saunders", 1985-1986 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 13)
  - Article: "Comments on the Paper by D. Clausse and F. Broto Entitled 'Influence of a Precooling on the Nucleation Kinetics of Ice from Water Droplets'", 1948-1983 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 14)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Three Dimensional Kinematic and Microphysical Evolution of Florida Cumulonimbus'", 1996 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Article: "Comment on 'Thunderstorm Electrification: The Effect of Cloud Droplets' by E.R. Jayaratne and C.P.R. Saunders", 1985-1987 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)
  - Article: "Comment on 'Trip Illumines Lightning' by R.D. Hill", 1995 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Article: "Comment on VLF Tramission Induced Slot Electron Precipitation", 1962; 1974; 1977-1978 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18)
  - Article: "Comments on 'Warm Rain Initiation :An Overview of Microphysical Mechanisms'", 1994-1995; 1997 (Box 2 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 19)